{
    "subject": "resource/Robert_Randolph_and_the_Family_Band",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Robert Randolph and the Family Band",
    "human_readable": "The name of Robert Randolph and the Family Band is Robert Randolph and the Family Band.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.973347544670105,
            "question": "Who leads Robert Randolph and the Family Band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9557697772979736,
            "question": "Where is Robert Randolph and the Family Band from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9356926083564758,
            "question": "Is 'Robert Randolph and the Family Band' a solo artist or a group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9133275747299194,
            "question": "What genre of music does Robert Randolph and the Family Band play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9036602973937988,
            "question": "What makes Robert Randolph and the Family Band unique?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8898711800575256,
            "question": "What instruments are typically used by Robert Randolph and the Family Band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8399161696434021,
            "question": "Has Robert Randolph and the Family Band released any albums?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7516536712646484,
            "question": "Are there other musicians besides Robert Randolph in the band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.733388364315033,
            "question": "Has Robert Randolph and the Family Band won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38106390833854675,
            "question": "What is the full name of the band?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Robert Randolph and the Family Band is Robert Randolph and the Family Band.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3020_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Robert Randolph and the Family Band won any awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3020_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there other musicians besides Robert Randolph in the band?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3020_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Robert Randolph and the Family Band released any albums?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3020_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3020_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3020_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3020_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3020_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3020_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3020_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3020_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3020_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3020_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3020_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the query in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that \"The name of Robert Randolph and the Family Band is Robert Randolph and the Family Band.\" This can be inferred from multiple documents, where the band's name is consistently referred to as \"Robert Randolph and the Family Band\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently refer to the band as \"Robert Randolph and the Family Band,\" which confirms the statement that the name of the band is indeed \"Robert Randolph and the Family Band.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}